Finding Aid for Sam Sturgis Photograph collection
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Ann Arbor
  - AA 250 - AA 275
    - View of Ann Arbor Art Fair in July 1969. 1969, AA 261.35 --; No neg. (Box 2)
    - View of Ann Arbor Art Fair in July 1969. 1969, AA 261.36 --; No neg. (Box 2)
    - View of Ann Arbor Art Fair in July 1969. 1969, AA 261.37 --; No neg. (Box 2)
    - View of Ann Arbor Art Fair in July 1969. 1969, AA 261.38 --; No neg. (Box 2)
    - View of Ann Arbor Art Fair in July 1969. 1969, AA 261.39 --; No neg. (Box 2)
    - View of Ann Arbor Art Fair in July 1969. 1969, AA 261.40 --; No neg. (Box 2)
    - View of Ann Arbor Art Fair in July 1969. 1969, AA 261.41 --; No neg. (Box 2)
    - View of Ann Arbor Art Fair in July 1969. 1969, AA 261.42 --; No neg. (Box 2)
    - View of Ann Arbor Art Fair in July 1969. 1969, AA 261.43 --; No neg. (Box 2)
    - Panoramic view of Ann Arbor on 3 May 1971. 1971, AA 262 --; No neg. (Box 2)
    - Ann Arbor Fire Department Banquet at main station in 1914. Chief Charles Andrews at head of table. 1914, AA 263 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Ann Arbor Fire Department Chief Charles Andrews., AA 264A --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Ann Arbor Fire Department Chief Ernest Heller., AA 264B --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Ann Arbor Fire Department Chief Ben J. Zahn., AA 264C --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Ann Arbor Fire Department Chief Arthur Stauch., AA 264D --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Octagon House built 1858 on North University Ave., present site of UM's Hill Auditorium. Photo taken 1892. Home of UM Professor Alexander Winchell. 1892, AA 265 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - First Lutheran Church built in 1833. Photo taken in 1881. 1881, AA 266A --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Exterior of Wadhams, Ryan and Reule Menswear located in Hangsterfer Building at 200-202 Main St. in 1898. 1898, AA 266.1 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
      (Source: Herb Sager.)
    - Interior of Fiegel's Menswear (possibly Wadhams, Ryan and Reule Menswear at 200-202 Main St.) at 322-324 South Main St. in 1932. 1932, AA 266.2 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Merchants Credit Association Banquet at Allenel Hotel in 1913. 1913, AA 266.3 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.1 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.2 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
      (Source and photographer. Sam Sturgis.)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.3 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.4 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.5 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.6 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.7 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.8 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.9 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.10 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.11 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.12 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.13 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.14 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.15 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.16 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.17 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.18 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.19 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
      (Source and photographer Sam Sturgis.)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.20 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.21 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.22 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.23 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.24 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.25 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.26 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.27 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.28 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.29 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.30 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.31 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.32 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.33 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.34 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.35 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 3)
    - Art Fair on South University Ave. July 21-24, 1971. 1971, AA 267.36 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 3)
    - Foster Mill foundations on Huron River, 11 August 1971. 1971, AA 268.1 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Foster Mill foundations on Huron River, 11 August 1971. 1971, AA 268.2 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Foster Mill foundations on Huron River, 11 August 1971. 1971, AA 268.3 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Foster Mill foundations on Huron River, 11 August 1971. 1971, AA 268.4 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Foster Mill foundations on Huron River, 11 August 1971. 1971, AA 268.5 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Foster Mill foundations on Huron River, 11 August 1971. 1971, AA 268.6 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Foster Mill foundations on Huron River, 11 August 1971. 1971, AA 268.7 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Foster Mill foundations on Huron River, 11 August 1971. 1971, AA 268.8 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Foster Mill foundations on Huron River, 11 August 1971. 1971, AA 268.9 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Ann Arbor Railroad Bridge and boat livery foundations on Huron River, 11 August 1971. 1971, AA 269.1 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Ann Arbor Railroad Bridge and boat livery foundations on Huron River, 11 August 1971. 1971, AA 269.2 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Ann Arbor Railroad Bridge and boat livery foundations on Huron River, 11 August 1971. 1971, AA 269.3 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Ann Arbor Railroad Bridge and boat livery foundations on Huron River, 11 August 1971. 1971, AA 269.4 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Ann Arbor Railroad Bridge and boat livery foundations on Huron River, 11 August 1971. 1971, AA 269.5 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Ann Arbor Railroad Bridge and boat livery foundations on Huron River, 11 August 1971. 1971, AA 269.6 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Ann Arbor Railroad Bridge and boat livery foundations on Huron River, 11 August 1971. 1971, AA 269.7 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Ann Arbor Railroad Bridge and boat livery foundations on Huron River, 11 August 1971. 1971, AA 269.8 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Ann Arbor Railroad Bridge and boat livery foundations on Huron River, 11 August, 1971. 1971, AA 269.9 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Ann Arbor Railroad Bridge and boat livery foundations on Huron River, 11 August 1971. 1971, AA 269.10 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Ann Arbor Railroad Bridge and boat livery foundations on Huron River, 11 August 1971. 1971, AA 269.11 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - First Volunteer Fire Department in Ann Arbor. The Defiance Hook and Ladder Company No. 1 in November 1877. Replaced by paid crew in 1888. 1877, AA 270.1 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Ann Arbor Fire Department ladder truck., AA 270.2 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Ann Arbor Fire Department main station no. 1 in 1967 at East Huron St. and Fifth Ave. 1967, AA 270.3 --; copy neg. Built 1882, National Register of Historic Places. (Box 3)
    - Ann Arbor Railroad Bridge accident., AA 271.1 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Ann Arbor Railroad Bridge accident. Built 1891, collapsed 1904., AA 271.2 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 3)
    - Ann Arbor Railroad depot c. 1885 as seen from Old Broadway Bridge. Bldg. moved for new depot and tall section made into house that stands on NE corner of N. Fifth Ave. and Beakes St. circa 1885, AA 271.3 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 3)
      (Source: MHC. Published.)
      [See also AA-29B]
    - Ann Arbor Railroad Bridge with passenger train c. 1885. circa 1885, AA 271.4 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Argo Dam on the Huron River and Ann Arbor Railroad bridge on 17 April 1910. 1910, AA 272.1 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
      (Source: Mrs. CC Ordway. Photographer: Goetz.)
    - Street alley on 20 April 1911. 1911, AA 272.2 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
      (Source Mrs. CC Ordway. Photographer: Goetz.)
    - Panoramic view of Ann Arbor from Butter Cup Hill, spring 1911. 1911, AA 272.3 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Exterior of Goetz Meat Market on 17 April 1910. 1910, AA 272.4 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Michigan Central Railroad Flyer in June 1910 toward Chicago by way of Dexter past icehouse on Argo Pond. 1910, AA 272.5 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Ann Arbor Railroad inter-city motor car on 30 May 1911. Called "Ping-Pong" train, went from AA to Whitmore Lake and back. 1911, AA 272.6 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
      (Published. Source: Mrs. CC Ordway. Photographer: Goetz.)
    - Merchant's Delivery Route One, August 1-5, 1911. 1911, AA 272.7 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Merchant's Delivery Route One, August 1-5, 1911. 1911, AA 272.8 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Ann Arbor Fire Department., AA 272.9 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - UM President Ruthven's house on East Vista on 18 May 1935. 1935, AA 273.1 --; copy neg. Swain photo 11861. (Box 3)
    - UM Women's Fieldhouse/Athletic Building on Palmer Field, erected 1928; razed 1974., AA 273.2 --; No neg. (Box 3)
      (Swain photo 9177.)
    - UM Barbour Gymnasium., AA 273.3 --; No neg. (Box 3)
      (Swain photo 6018.)
    - UM University Hall., AA 273.4 --; No neg. (Box 3)
      (Swain photo 12684.)
    - UM East Engineering Building as seen from steps of Physics Building., AA 273.5 --; copy neg. Swain 11863. (Box 3)
    - UM East Engineering Building on 19 May 1935. 1935, AA 273.6 --; copy neg. Swain 11864. (Box 3)
    - Telephoto view of UM Hospital., AA 273.7 --; copy neg. Swain 11881. (Box 3)
    - UM Professor Alexander Winchell's former residence, now site of Hill Auditorium on North University Ave., AA 273.8 --; copy neg. Swain 12509. (Box 3)
    - UM Observatory., AA 273.9 --; No neg. (Box 3)
      (Swain 6089.)
    - UM Observatory., AA 273.10 --; No neg. (Box 3)
    - UM South Hall., AA 273.11A --; copy neg. Swain 12510 (Box 3)
    - UM professor's residence., AA 273.11B --; copy neg. Swain 12510 (?). (Box 3)
      [See also AA 273.8.]
    - UM Library., AA 273.11C --; copy neg. Swain 12510 (Box 3)
    - UM building, possibly Economics or Pharmacology. Bicycle also in photo., AA 273.11D --; copy neg. Swain 12510 (?). (Box 3)
    - View of UM tennis courts from Mosher-Jordan dormitory., AA 273.12 --; No neg. (Box 3)
      (Swain photo 9758.)
    - Street and residences., AA 273.13 --; No neg. (Box 3)
      (Swain photo 6461.)
    - UM Law Building., AA 273.14 --; copy neg. Swain photo 9580. Law Building renamed Haven Hall in 1933. Destroyed by fire in 1950. (Box 3)
    - UM Observatory., AA 273.15 --; No neg. (Box 3)
      (Swain photo 6089A.)
    - Man, possibly UM person?, AA 273.16 --; copy neg. Swain photo? (Box 3)
    - UM University Hall until 1950. Angell Hall built in front in 1922., AA 273.17 --; No neg. (Box 3)
      (Swain photo 9525.)
    - UM Observatory., AA 273.18 --; No neg. (Box 3)
    - Construction, possibly on UM campus, on 22 August 1927. 1927, AA 273.19 --; No neg. (Box 3)
      (Swain photo (?)
    - View of Observatory Hill and stacks of heating plant from steps of University Hospital. In 1911, another larger reflecting telescope added., AA 273.20 --; No neg. (Box 3)
      (Swain photo 9537)
    - Kitchen inside the UM Women's Athletic Building., AA 273.21 --; No neg. No print.. (Box 3)
      (Swain 9547.)
    - UM University Hall., AA 273.22 --; No neg. (Box 3)
      (Swain photo 12683.)
    - Broadway, Beakes Ave. and Detroit St. intersection., AA 273.23 --; No neg. (Box 3)
      (Swain photo 13165.)
    - Quarry House at corner Cambridge St. and Washtenaw Ave. in 1921. 1921, AA 273.24 --; copy neg. Swain photo 6442. (Box 3)
    - Quarry House from Ferdon St. on 28 April 1921. 1921, AA 273.25 --; copy neg. Swain photo 6443. (Box 3)
    - Residence of Dr. Dean W. Myers on Washtenaw Ave., presently part of the Unitarian Church., AA 273.26 --; copy neg. Swain photo 6674. (Box 3)
    - Front-terrace wall and southwest corner of Hoover Place. 1921, AA 273.27 --; copy neg. Swain photo 6672. (Box 3)
    - UM Angell Hall on 10 May 1930. 1930, AA 273.28 --; No neg.
      (Swain photo 12183.)
    - Interior lobby view of Michigan Union., AA 273.29 --; No neg. (Box 3)
      (Swain photo 5683.)
    - Corner of Liberty and Maynard Sts. on 5 August 1935. 1935, AA 273.30 --; No neg. (Box 3)
      (Swain photo 11942.)
    - Cedar Bend Drive, downhill below hairpin turn., AA 273.31 --; copy neg. Swain photo 8661. (Box 3)
    - Entrance to UM Arboretum in 1907. 1907, AA 273.32 --; copy neg. Swain photo 8760. (Box 3)
    - Grandstand at Ferry Field 1923, AA 273.33 --; copy neg. Swain photo 8100. (Box 3)
    - Front of UM Haven Hall with Angell Hall in background on 10 May 1936. 1936, AA 273.34 --; copy neg. Swain photo 12184. (Box 3)
    - Staebler gas station on State St., AA 273.35 --; No neg. (Box 3)
      (Swain photo 12198.)
    - Residence of Mrs. Henry W. Douglas., AA 273.36 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - UM Architecture Building., AA 273.37 --; No neg. (Box 3)
      (Swain photo 12182.)
    - Machine Specialty Company on 10 October 1927. 1927, AA 273.38 --; copy neg. Swain photo 9254. Factory on North Main St. by Argo Pond. MCRR engine next to river. (Box 3)
    - UM ROTC Building., AA 273.39 --; No neg. (Box 3)
      (Swain photo 9242.)
    - Methodist Church on 8 May 1921. 1921, AA 273.40 --; copy neg. Swain photo 6467. (Box 3)
    - UM University Hall., AA 273.41 --; copy neg. Swain photo 11957. (Box 3)
    - UM Professor Bartell's residence., AA 273.42 --; copy neg. Swain photo (?) (Box 3)
    - UM building?, AA 273.43 --; copy neg. Swain photo 9521. (Box 3)
    - UM building under construction?, AA 273.44 --; copy neg. Swain photo 13029. (Box 3)
    - UM campus view?, AA 273.45 --; copy neg. Swain photo 5682. (Box 3)
    - UM University Hospital from Cedar Bend Drive., AA 273.46 --; copy neg. Swain 1111. (Box 3)
    - UM new Dental School Building in 1906 on North University Ave. 1906, AA 273.47 --; copy neg. Swain 11132. (Box 3)
    - UM University Hospital seen from Observatory on 27 September 1931. Hospital established in 1925. 1931, AA 273.48 --; copy neg. Swain photo 11168A. (Box 3)
    - South End of University High School Library c. 1930. circa 1930, AA 273.49 --; No neg. (Box 3)
      (Swain photo 13151A.)
    - Portrait of Dr. H.B. Hutchins. (UM professor?), AA 273.50 --; No neg. (Box 3)
      (Swain photo 9929.)
    - Swain photo 8945., AA 273.51 --; No neg. (Box 3)
      (Swain photo 8945.)
    - Cascade Glen Bird Hills Colony on 20 April 1927. 1927, AA 273.52 --; No neg. (Box 3)
    - UM University Museum as seen from the east on 25 January 1921. 1921, AA 273.53 --; copy neg. Swain photo 6315. Museum later known as Language Building. Designed by William Le Baron Jenney. (Box 3)
    - View of Hoover Place from southwest, with LJ Hoover residence, later site of Youth for Understanding on Washtenaw Ave. 1921, AA 273.54 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
      (Published. Source: Swain photo 6671.)
    - Botanical Gardens off Packard St. 1928, AA 273.55 --; No neg. (Box 3)
      (Swain photo 9427.)
    - "My-T-Fine" Cafe exterior at 101-105 South Thayer St., AA 273.56 --; copy neg. Swain photo 6693. (Box 3)
    - "My-T-Fine" Cafe interior toward rear of building at 101-105 South Thayer St., AA 273.59 --; copy neg. Swain photo 6695. (Box 3)
    - Congregational Church on 8 May 1921. 1921, AA 273.60 --; copy neg. Swain photo 6463. (Box 3)
    - Congregational Church on 8 May 1921. 1921, AA 273.61 --; copy neg. Swain photo 6464. (Box 3)
    - View of Observatory from new University Hospital., AA 273.62 --; copy neg. Swain photo 6446A. (Box 3)
    - Catherine St. Hospital viewed from new University Hospital. 1921, AA 273.63 --; copy neg. Swain photo 6444. (Box 3)
    - View of Cedar Bend Drive and Fuller Road as seen from new University Hospital on 28 April 1921. 1921, AA 273.64 --; copy neg. Swain photo 6445. (Box 3)
    - UM Law Department(?)., AA 273.65A --; copy neg. Swain photo 11135A. (Box 3)
    - UM Law Department(?)., AA 273.65B --; copy neg. Swain photo 11135B. (Box 3)
    - Residence of UM professor Dr. R. Bishop Canfield on Washtenaw Ave. in July 1920. Present site of Women's City Club. 1920, AA 273.66 --; copy neg. Swain photo 6080A. (Box 3)
    - UM Architecture Building, monuments and yard as seen from southwest. 1931, AA 273.67 --; copy neg. Swain photo 11141. (Box 3)
    - Maple tree at Bird Hills Colony on 20 April 1927. 1927, AA 273.68 --; No neg. (Box 3)
      (Swain photo 8949.)
    - Cherry tree at Bird Hills Colony on 20 April 1927. 1927, AA 273.69 --; No neg. (Box 3)
      (Swain photo 8942.)
    - Shagbark tree at Bird Hills Colony on 20 April 1927. 1927, AA 273.70A --; No neg. (Box 3)
      (Swain photo 8948.)
    - [Undescribed], AA 273.70B --; No neg. (Box 3)
    - Barton Dam and Powerhouse as seen from Bird Hills Colony on 20 April 1927. 1927, AA 273.70C --; No neg. (Box 3)
    - Sentinel Elm tree at Bird Hills Colony on 20 April 1927. 1922, AA 273.71 --; copy neg. swain photo 8943. (Box 3)
    - Icehouses on Huron River., AA 274.1 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
      [See also AA 232.7]
    - Baumgartner Stone Works., AA 274.2 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Scenic view of northeast Ann Arbor from Sheraton Ann Arbor Hotel., AA 275 --; No neg. (Box 3)
  - AA 276- AA 300
    - John S. Seaver family farm and home four miles south of Ypsilanti in 1897. 1897, AA 276 --; No neg.
    - Airplane made by Don Gregory crashed on roof of Cook Spring Building in 1913 on Ferry Field. 1913, AA 277.1 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
      [See also AA 260 and AA 277.]
    - Airplane made by Don Gregory nose down on Ferry Field in 1914. 1914, AA 277.2 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
      [See also AA 260 and 277.1]
    - Airplane., AA 278.1 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Airplane., AA 278.2 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Airplane., AA 278.3 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - State St. in 1933. 1933, AA 279 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Drake's Sandwich Shop opened in 1929 at 709 North University Ave., AA 280 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Eastern Michigan Edison Company Barton Plant. Construction of Barton Dam and Powerhouse in 1912. Ernie Allmendinger holds horses reins. 1912, AA 281.1 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Cornwell Mill, built in 1885, burned 8 May 1913. stood where Huron River Dr * now bends south to join Main St., AA 281.2 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Cornwell Mill burning on 8 May 1913. 1913, AA 281.3 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Ladies Library Association Building in 1885 on south side of Huron St. between Fifth Ave and Division Sts. 1885, AA 282.1 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Ann Arbor residences in March 1896. 1896, AA 282.2 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Ann Arbor bridge in April 1896. 1896, AA 282.3 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Mew Depot at Geddesburg in August 1896. 1896, AA 282.5 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 3)
    - Fleming Creek Dam in September 1896. 1896, AA 282.6 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 3)
    - Fleming Creek Bridge in September 1896. 1896, AA 282.7 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Railroad bridge., AA 283 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - County building and Allenel Hotel., AA 284 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Interior view of factory with Mr. Most standing third from right., AA 285 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 3)
    - Olgo Bolgos at Parker Mill Cabin., AA 286 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Presbyterian Church., AA 287 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Southwest corner of Main and Washington Sts., Hangsterfer Building in 1908. 1908, AA 288 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Northwest corner of Packard and State Sts., including Fisher and Finnells Grocery Store and Merchants Delivery Co., c. 1910. circa 1910, AA 289 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Bob Livesay at W.L. McCullough Company., AA 290 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - View of Main St. south from Ann St. "Lost In New York" playing at Opera House in the 1890s. 1892, AA 291 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
      (Published in Washtenaw Art Works 1892.)
    - Bridge at Geddes Road., AA 292 --; No neg. (Box 3)
    - Ann Arbor Public Library on 15 Sept. 1916. 1916, AA 295 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - UM Engineering Lab in 1894. 1894, AA 296 --; copy neg. RH Scadin photo. (Box 3)
    - Dean and Company and Ann Arbor Railroad freight depot c.1900. Passenger depot across tracks. circa 1900, AA 297 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 3)
    - Allen Creek c. 1900. Houses on hill at left face Ashley St. Dean and Co. Warehouse at right on First St., torn down in 1914. circa 1900, AA 298 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - William St., AA 299 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 3)
    - Delhi after cyclone in April 1916. 1916, AA 300.1 --; No neg. (Box 3)
    - Delhi after cyclone in April 1916. 1916, AA 300.2 --; No neg. (Box 3)
    - Delhi after cyclone in April 1916. 1916, AA 300.3 --; No neg. (Box 3)
  - AA 301 - AA 350
    - Fred Rettich's Orchestra Hall., AA 301 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - John Wagner Sr. residence at northwest corner West Washington and Ashley Sts., AA 302 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Hutzel's Hustlers team., AA 303 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Otto's Band in 1912. 1912, AA 304 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 3)
    - Employees of Allmendinger organ Company at corner First and Washington Sts., AA 305 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Markham Pottery., AA 306 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Dr. Chase's Steam Printing House c. 1870. circa 1870, AA 307 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Northwest corner Main and Huron Sts. c. 1905. circa 1905, AA 308 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Central Flouring Mill of the Michigan milling company c. 1902. owned by Allmendinger and Schneider. 1902, AA 309 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Blaich Brothers grocers in Chelsea. George Blaich in photo., AA 310 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Interior of Dean and Company at 214 South Main St., AA 311 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Exterior of Dean and Company at 214 South Main St. in 1894 or 1985. Dean and Co. sold groceries and china. circa 1895, AA 312 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Interior of Postal Telegraph Cable Company in Cornwell Buildings, then called Hamilton Block in mid-1890s on Huron St. and N. Fourth Ave. circa 1895, AA 313 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
      [See also AA-221.7 and AA-221.8.]
    - Old Brick Antique Shop later the Yankee Trader at 512 South Main St., AA 314 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
    - Blaich Brothers grocers in Chelsea with George Blaich in door with A. Gates and Beissel?, AA 315 --; copy neg. (Box 3)
      [See also AA 310]